[
    {
        "QuestionNum": "1",
        "Question": "What is the castle that Harry attends?",
        "A": "Beauxbaton",
        "B": "Hogwarts",
        "C": "Durmstrang",
        "D": "Ilvermorny",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "2",
        "Question": "Who was headmaster at Hogwarts before Dumbledore?",
        "A": "Dexter Fortescue",
        "B": "Dilys Derwent",
        "C": "Phineas Nigellus Black",
        "D": "Armando Dippet",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "3",
        "Question": "In the later books, Buckbeak gets a secret name in order to protect his identity. What was this nickname?",
        "A": "Witherwings",
        "B": "Griphook",
        "C": "Hokey",
        "D": "Billywig",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "4",
        "Question": "Who was Aragog's wife?",
        "A": "Ungoliant",
        "B": "Kelpie",
        "C": "Mosag",
        "D": "Matagot",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "5",
        "Question": "Who was the Ministry of Magic employee who investigates Morfin's crimes?",
        "A": "Bob Ogden",
        "B": "Yaxley",
        "C": "Kingsley Shacklebolt",
        "D": "Ludovic Bagman",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "6",
        "Question": "What was Rita Skeeter's animagus form?",
        "A": "Cat",
        "B": "Beetle",
        "C": "Mouse",
        "D": "Bird",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "7",
        "Question": "Who was the leader of the Centaur's?",
        "A": "Magorian",
        "B": "Firenze",
        "C": "Bane",
        "D": "Ronan",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "8",
        "Question": "Which of Voldemort's Death Eaters was an unspeakable?",
        "A": "Antonin Dolohov",
        "B": "Thorfinn Rowle",
        "C": "Scabior",
        "D": "Augustus Rookwood",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "9",
        "Question": "What is the magic number that appears all throughout the Harry Potter story?",
        "A": "5",
        "B": "8",
        "C": "7",
        "D": "3",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "10",
        "Question": "How many staircases are in Hogwarts?",
        "A": "142",
        "B": "100",
        "C": "150",
        "D": "200",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "11",
        "Question": "What vault number do Hagrid and Harry stop at first in the Philosopher's Stone?",
        "A": "687",
        "B": "713",
        "C": "394",
        "D": "777",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "12",
        "Question": "Who planted the Whomping Willow?",
        "A": "Lupin",
        "B": "Dumbledore",
        "C": "Dippet",
        "D": "Merlin",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "13",
        "Question": "What is Dumbledore's full name?",
        "A": "Albus Wulfric Brian Percival Dumbledore",
        "B": "Albus Percival Brian Wulfric Dumbledore",
        "C": "Albus Brian Wulfric Percival Dumbledore",
        "D": "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "14",
        "Question": "What are the small pale-green skinned creatures that reside in the black Lake alongside the Merpeople and the Giant squid?",
        "A": "Flobberworm",
        "B": "Kelpie",
        "C": "Grindylow",
        "D": "Marmite",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "15",
        "Question": "Who was Ollivander's competition in making and selling wands?",
        "A": "Mykew Gregorovitch",
        "B": "Gellert Grindelwald",
        "C": "Rolanda Hooch",
        "D": "Aurora Sinistra",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "16",
        "Question": "Who killed Helena Ravenclaw?",
        "A": "Fat Friar",
        "B": "Bloody Baron",
        "C": "Cuthbert Binns",
        "D": "Sir Nicholas de Mimsey Porpington",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "17",
        "Question": "How many years had passed between the first opening of the Chamber of Secrets and the second?",
        "A": "50",
        "B": "100",
        "C": "150",
        "D": "200",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "18",
        "Question": "What page does Snape have the students turn to when he teaches a class of Defence Against the Dark Arts in Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "A": "200",
        "B": "687",
        "C": "567",
        "D": "394",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "19",
        "Question": "How many Sickles equals one Galleon?",
        "A": "29",
        "B": "15",
        "C": "17",
        "D": "10",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "20",
        "Question": "Who gave the original prophecy involving Harry and Voldemort?",
        "A": "Sybill Trelawney",
        "B": "Albus Dumbledore",
        "C": "Serious Black",
        "D": "Minerva McGonagall",
        "Answer": "A"
    }
]